Contact

sammyjjr@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sam-jones-a2621390 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Leadership
Strategic Planning and Execution
Employee Engagement

Certifications
Registered Nurse

Sam Jones

VP Patient Care Services (CNO)

Corvallis, Oregon Area

Summary

Experienced Chief Nursing Officer and servant leader with major focus on community, employee engagement, physician relations, strategic planning and execution, and the patient experience. Expert in process re-engineering and change management. Personal Axiom: To provide safe quality care and excellent service to every patient every time.

Experience

Samaritan Pacific Communities Hospital Vice President Patient Care Services May 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months) Newport, OR, United States

Carlsbad Medical Center (CHS)
Chief Nursing Officer
September 2016 - May 2019 (2 years 9 months)
Carlsbad, NewMexico

MatSu Regional Medical Center (CHS)
Assistant Chief Nursing Officer and Director of Critical Care Services
October 2013 - September 2016 (3 years)

Palmer, Alaska

Mercy Medical Center (CHI)

Director of the Emergency Department and Trauma Services
October 2010 - October 2013 (3 years 1 month)
Roseburg, Oregon

Education

University of Phoenix
Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse

University of Phoenix Master's degree, Nursing Administration